How do you explain the inexplicable?
You don't.
You just...
surrender to it.
You move on.
Why? Because...
...what other choice is there?
The thing about Cable though,
if you knew her,
you'd know...
...she wasn't easy to move on from.
She wasn't easy to quit.
Take it from me. I hired her.
I fired her. I hired her again.
But, hey,
Cable wouldn't want us to cry too hard
or cry too long.
She would want to know
that we all got together
at her favorite hang,
had a bunch of beers,
put some...
of her favorite songs on the jukebox...
and remembered all those nutty T-shirts.
To Cable.
If there's anything I can do,
anything at all, don't hesitate to call.
What?
That's okay. I can have
my husband take care of it.
The police called last night.
They recovered some things from the car.
From her...
They said I could come
pick 'em up, but I...
It's okay. We can do that.
We'll take care of that.
And then we can bring them to you.
Or not.
Whatever you decide.
Hey, Marissa, can you put
the TV on?
Channel 3.
And if you are just joining us,
we have a late-breaking
development to tell you about.
According to investigators,
they now believe
a single member of the 40-person crew
performing routine maintenance
on this bridge less than three weeks ago
embedded plastic explosives
and a remote timer in one small section
- of the bridge's undercarriage.
- That's the bridge that Cable...
The question now is,
if this wasn't a case
of infrastructure failure,
but rather an act
of sabotage, perhaps even an act
of terrorism,
who was behind it and why?
I don't have an answer, Ellen.
It's a horrible world.
We do unspeakable things to each other.
I wish...
I understood why.
Absolutely.
Whatever you need.
Whatever the hour.
I'm here.
You call.
I'm not gonna drop dead
from a sip of whiskey.
You don't know that.
I might kill you.
- Did you tell him?
- He was on the phone.
- Tell him what?
- They found the terrorists.
Found the cell.
Where? When?
They were all killed.
Somewhere in Prague.
And according to reports,
no one is taking credit for
the bridge collapse on purpose.
They wanted to make it look
like an accident.
They wanted to make us afraid of
everything we take for granted.
During the raid, they found
plans for, uh, 25 more...
what did they call those... events.
Now they're checking all over
the country to make sure
that none of those
were put into motion.
So what do we do now?
Nothing. Nothing.
There's-there's nothing we can do.
Leave here, we get in an elevator,
we hope that no one has messed with it.
We get on the subway,
and we hope that's safe, too.
You know, they've won.
They've taken that
certainty away from us.
They've taken away our confidence.
And they've taken Cable.
Hello?
Really?
Sure.
Send him up.
Send who up?
It's, like, 3:00 in the morning.
I just kept thinking
about what Benny said.
How there was nothing to do.
Nothing to do but embrace fear.
Time for breakfast?
Eh, somewhere in the world.
Sorry about the intrusion.
No, you're not.
Nice speech the other day.
We haven't officially met.
I'm Greg.
I'm her husband.
I'm Jason. I'm her...
I know who you are.
This midnight caller thing,
you do this a lot?
- No.
- Yes.
You want something stronger than that?
- No.
- Yes.
So, here's my question.
How do you do this?
Plastic explosives.
Remote timers. Passports.
20-some other events. Training.
It all costs money, right?
I mean, you have to house people.
You have to feed people.
Okay...
So... where does
all this money come from?
Maybe a foreign government somewhere.
Yeah.
But how do you get it here?
To America.
How do you pay for all
this stuff, all these people?
You need credit cards,
bank accounts, cash.
Sounds like you need... a bank.
Bingo.
Marissa, you must know someone
at the U.S. attorney's office
that specializes in terrorism.
I do. But, Bull,
the terrorists are all dead.
Who is it you're looking to go after?
The folks that killed Cable.
The folks who helped pay
for that bridge to come down.
They bank with Thoreau Financial.
A grand old 120-year-old American bank
with branches all over the world.
Your mom and dad probably had
a mortgage with them.
So why aren't you guys
over there right now,
guns blazing, throwing whoever's
allowing this to happen
into prison?
Well, we would if we could.
Thoreau Financial was
actually investigated
by the Senate Banking Committee in 2010.
Then again in 2014.
Then again last year.
They were cleared of any wrongdoing
each and every time.
But how is that possible?
You know, when my old
Homeland buddy Marissa called
and asked me if I'd meet
with the great Jason Bull,
I never would've guessed what
a babe in the woods you'd be.
Was that meant to offend me?
Never been called a babe before.
Have you ever heard of John Honaker?
He's the CEO of Thoreau.
Basically, he is Thoreau.
He bought it in 2008
after the financial crisis.
He took a string of small
mom-and-pop community banks
and he built it into
a multibillion dollar
financial institution.
No, you'll never get Thoreau.
People have tried. I've tried.
You bring down Thoreau Financial
and the repercussions will
affect the entire economy.
So that's that?
That is that.
What about that guy?
What guy?
The guy who runs it all.
Honaker?
- What if I just went after him?
- This is
John Honaker, the CEO
of Thoreau Financial.
This is what he had to say
on television this morning.
All of us at Thoreau Financial
were shocked when we learned
earlier today
that the terrorists responsible
for that bridge collapse
apparently used our bank
to facilitate their horrific activities.
To be clear, we are in contact
with Homeland Security, the CIA, the NSA,
and both local and
international law enforcement.
We're going to do everything we can
to get to the bottom of this,
to try and understand why
it happened, how it happened,
and to make sure that nothing
like this ever happens again.
In the meantime,
our prayers and sympathies
are with the victims and their families.
And according to Bull,
he's our target.
We're not prosecutors.
We can't bring any criminal
charges against him.
And as far as a civil lawsuit goes,
we cannot sue on Cable's behalf.
We are her employers, not her family.
Seems like a fairly minor technicality.
Oh, my goodness. Dr. Bull.
How can I say no?
Why would I say no?
It might be painful.
Reliving it again.
I'll be filing the suit on your behalf,
so you may have reporters
knocking on your door.
As for court,
you don't have to be there every day.
I will pay for everything.
Still...
you might want to discuss it
with your husband.
I love my husband.
But, uh,
he's not Cable's real father.
And, frankly, this is my call.
I don't suppose you've ever lost
a child, Dr. Bull.
Make it hurt.
I'm sure gonna try.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Look at me.
I'm looking.
I'm not Cable.
Thanks for that.
The resemblance is startling.
I'm an investigator.
And this is not a case
that you learn on, Bull.
This is a case that you-you go out
and you get the very best po...
I've got this.
But he needs to hear that we...
Really.
I've got this.
See you in the morning.
You see that pile of papers on
the left-hand side of your desk?
Oh, my God, it's the Da Vinci Code.
Who knew? It's been here the whole time?
- I better call Tom Hanks.
- Those are résumés.
They have been here for three weeks.
Okay, look, I don't want
to replace her, either.
None of us do.
It seems... callous and final,
and I hate it, but if you want
- to win this thing...
- Well, I can't do it.
I can't...
sit here with strangers
and interview them and pretend
that I'm excited they're here.
Well, then you don't get to pick.
I'm getting someone
in here ASAP. I have to.
I'm heading home.
I will start to make calls
as soon as I get there.
Then I'm going to bed.
So... I'll see you tomorrow.
What do you mean?
Tomorrow? In the morning,
as opposed to later tonight?
Oh, come on.
That was fun.
And yes, you'll see me in the morning
and not before.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'll just be here
for a few more hours.
Need to do a couple of miles
on the hamster wheel
over there, and then start
learning everything I can
about Honaker and his lawyer.
Don't stay here too late.
And, look... don't
fall asleep in your office.
And don't drink.
Can I at least have a few friends over,
have a small party?
I promise to clean up.
Dad said it was okay.
Night, John-Boy.
Night, Elizabeth.
Hello?
Hey!
Oh, my gosh!
You scared me.
Sorry about the music.
Helps me stay awake when I work.
Oh, but I am so glad to see you.
All these trash cans have food in them,
And they're really starting to smell.
Miss?
Who the hell are you and how in the world
did you get in here?
Did they not tell you
someone was working tonight?
I'm supposed to be here.
I promise. See? Credentials.
You do not comport yourself
like someone who does office maintenance.
My name is Dr. Jason Bull.
These are my offices.
Oh, my gosh.
You're him?
Sh... ugar.
I had no idea.
These belong to Marissa Morgan.
I know. She's the one who called me.
I'm Taylor.
Taylor Rentzel.
She and I worked together at Homeland.
She said you guys needed a bunch
of cyber-sleuthing done ASAP.
And as it turns out, tonight's the night
my three-year-old...
goes to my ex for two days, so...
Oh. Was that him on the phone?
Child on the left, ex on the right.
Mauricio.
And moron.
And Mauricio's very beautiful.
Actually, uh, moron's
kind of pretty, too.
This is Ivan Gronsky,
and as I'm sure you've read,
he's the leader of the cell
that took down that bridge.
Right. And he was killed along
with the rest of his cell
during the CIA raid in Prague.
- Right you are.
- Mm-hmm.
So why are we wasting our time
talking about a dead man?
Because... at least the way
Marissa explained it to me...
you're trying to prove
that this guy personally used
his bank to launder money
so the bad guys could do...
bad things.
That is the working theory, yes.
So I've been looking
for points of intersection
between this guy and anyone
connected with this cell.
And by "points of
intersection," you mean...?
Any time banker fellow
and anyone from the cell
might have been at the same
place at the same time.
Or, in this case,
just on the same continent
at the same time.
- Okay.
- And as it happens,
for about a six-month period,
Mr. Gronsky lived in America.
Really? And what was he doing here?
He spent a semester
at an Ivy League school.
Do tell.
And guess who else
attended the same school,
three years ahead but at the same time?
Scrooge McDuck.
Thank you for doing this.
I'm sorry I frightened you before.
I'm going to leave you now,
so you can dance, dance, dance.
And you're hired, by the way.
Did Marissa already talk money or...
Rein it in there, big guy.
I'm not hired,
because I already have a job.
I work for Homeland Security.
Specialize in international banking.
And, uh, there is no pay,
because I'm not allowed
to do this if there is.
Homeland policy.
This is a favor for my friend Marissa.
And it's just for two days.
Hmm.
But it was a pleasure to meet you.
A pleasure to be met.
And again, thank you...
so much.
Anytime.
Can I help? He worked late.
Yeah. Well, I... just got a love letter
from Thoreau Financial.
Motion to dismiss.
Ms. George, I read
your motion to dismiss,
all 220 pages of it.
If I could trouble you
to restate your argument...
briefly... as to why
I should dismiss this case?
Thank you, Your Honor.
And let me begin by saying
that our hearts go out to the victims
of the I-99 Bridge collapse
and to their families.
But while we grieve for the victims,
we take strong exception to the assertion
that Mr. Honaker is somehow involved
or personally responsible.
And given the complete lack of evidence
to support such an outrageous assertion,
dismissal seems like
the only just course of action.
Mr. Colón,
you haven't presented the court
with much information.
Yes, we know that, Your Honor.
Unfortunately, all of the
relevant transactional records
are in the possession
of Thoreau Financial.
All we're asking for is a chance
to examine their records.
Which is the very definition
of a fishing expedition.
Ooh, there's nothing wrong with fishing.
Sometimes you hook a marlin.
What are you afraid of, Ms. George?
Mr. Colón.
Your Honor,
terrorists have struck our soil.
37 people are dead,
including my client's daughter.
All of the victim's families...
every American, for that matter...
is entitled to transparency.
They're entitled to the truth.
Motion to dismiss denied.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- But barely. I'm allowing this
to go to trial, but if you don't
come up with more than this,
I won't hesitate to pull the plug.
Ms. George, I'm ordering you
to comply with the plaintiff's
discovery requests.
They're trying to paper us
into submission.
Yeah. I can see exactly
what they're doing.
400,000 pages of transactions,
250 million routing records.
Every time little Timmy got
a ten dollar birthday
check from his nana,
it's in there.
Hmm. Can you call them
and thank them
for their exceptional response
to our request,
but see if they couldn't send us
their digital files?
Now that we have a new Cable.
- We have a new Cable?
- We have a temporary Taylor.
Mrs. McCrory.
Ellen.
What's that expression?
"If it looks like a duck
and quacks like a duck,
then it's probably a duck"?
Sorry, you lost me at the first duck.
A man came to my home early this morning.
He knocked on my door.
He would not explicitly identify himself
as working for Thoreau or Mr. Honaker,
but he did let me know
in no uncertain terms
that a $10 million settlement
was not out of the question
if... I were to drop my lawsuit.
What'd you say?
I told him to go duck himself.
You okay?
Kind of pleased, actually.
I mean, th-they're basically
admitting they did it,
aren't they?
If you give somebody money like that,
try to get them to go away...
That's exactly what it means.
We're making progress.
Yeah.
But we haven't made it hurt yet.
This trial's about banking and coding
and transactions and details.
We need people who are
gonna be able to absorb
bits of minutiae and not be overwhelmed.
Which means Honaker's lawyers
will be looking for the opposite...
jurors with short attention spans.
People who, when confronted
with the enormity
of complicated evidence, will tune out.
Do you own a smartphone, sir?
It's a phone.
Okay. And has anyone ever
texted you a photo on it?
Yeah. I-I think.
All right. Well,
let's just assume someone has,
and let's assume that you
wanted to share that photo
with juror number eight.
Can you take me through
the steps involved
for you to re-text that photo?
No.
You touch the picture,
and you drag it to his phone.
And how do you do that?
You just... you just drag it
as hard as you can.
You touch it,
the picture or the text message
you're trying to send.
That highlights it.
Once it's highlighted,
an icon will appear with the arrow.
You highlight that, and a dialogue box
will appear asking for the phone
number you want to text to.
You enter the phone number,
and you press send.
Okay.
I've got a riddle.
Your Honor...
I like riddles.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Now, a man has a fox, a duck,
and a bag of beans.
And he has to get them across the river,
but he can only take one at a time.
Now, if he leaves the fox with the duck,
the fox will eat the duck.
If he leaves the duck with the beans,
the duck will eat the beans.
How is he...?
I'm getting rid of all of them.
Wait, why? They know the answer.
No. They just think they do.
There is no answer.
So, here's the good news.
You have a case.
The bad news is
it's a circumstantial case.
We've won with circumstantial.
Well, you won't win with this one.
The terrorist accounts
should have been red-flagged
by the bank's own
internal auditing system,
and they weren't.
A problem with the program?
I'm sure that's what
they want you to think.
But then I found 71
other suspicious activity alerts
that the bank was all over, immediately.
But not Gronsky's.
- Not Gronsky's.
- You find any
direct connection between
Honaker and the terrorist?
Now that you mention it,
apparently Honaker was in Panama
with a group of bankers
two days after that bridge came down.
And that matters because...?
I cheated. I ran an NSA check.
Gronsky was off the grid at that time,
and the soft intel suggests
he was probably in Panama.
That's really great.
But it's still not conclusive.
We made a point to pick a jury
that would pay attention to the details,
follow a fact pattern,
not leap to conclusions.
We really need proof.
Hard proof.
Sorry to eat and run. My day care closes
in 25 minutes. I'll be in early tomorrow.
7:30-ish. Nice to meet you, Danny,
Benny, Chuck.
Chunk.
Well, other than screwing up
my name, she's very impressive.
Yeah, nice work, Marissa.
Well, we only have her for one more day,
so let's use her while we can.
Anything else on the investigative front?
Yeah, I've got something.
So, I've been tracking down
former employees who might
be able to shed some light
on Honaker and Thoreau,
and I found this independent contractor
who was hired to write
banking code for Thoreau.
His specialty is defeating
governmental safeguard systems.
Bingo.
- You think he'll talk to us?
- Well,
everyone I've approached
with any connection to the company
is either afraid to speak
or has signed an NDA.
Including this guy, Adam Shaw.
I-I don't get it.
If he won't speak to us...
if he can't speak to us...
Well, the thing is, uh, he's dying.
Stage IV lymphoma.
Well, nothing to lose.
Chuck, bring him in. Do your magic.
I know you had me served with a subpoena,
but I'm honestly not sure
I can be of any help to you.
I only worked at Thoreau for nine months.
Oh, let me be the judge
of that, Mr. Shaw.
- So, you write code?
- When I'm well enough
to work, which is not
terribly often these days.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask you about John Honaker?
About Thoreau Financial?
Y-You know I'm-I'm not supposed
to tell you anything.
You know they made me sign an NDA.
Yeah, but...
I know you know there are 37 people dead.
And a lot of times, that changes things.
Mr. Shaw, how did you come to apply
for a job at Thoreau?
I-I didn't apply
for the job. They-they sought me out.
And when you say "they"...?
I was... I was hired directly
by Mr. Honaker.
He seemed to know exactly who I was
and exactly what I did.
And this was shortly after
the terrorist Ivan Gronsky
opened up his accounts at Thoreau?
- That's correct.
- And at that time,
did Mr. Honaker explain
to you exactly what he wanted?
He couldn't have been more specific.
Uh, my first assignment
was to create a backdoor code.
And for those of us
who don't speak computer,
what is a backdoor code?
I-It's a type of bypass key.
Um, it's a piece of code
created specifically
to work around the regulatory protocols
set up by the U.S. government
to detect suspicious transactions.
Everybody following along?
They're hanging on his every word.
That must have raised
some concerns for you.
I mean, the president
of a bank asks you to
create some software
so that he can defeat
government safeguards.
I mean...
yes and no. I guess it should have.
The truth is
that I didn't specifically know
what they were going to use the code for.
Sometimes banks keep it
as a... fail-safe.
They know a transaction is good,
and they don't want
the government freezing it
or flagging it.
I mean, I didn't
specifically know
that Thoreau was going to use it
to thwart the AML or KYC protocols.
Again, a little help, sir.
AML are anti-money laundering programs.
KYC stands for "know your clients."
Uh, every bank is required to have them.
Okay, so you create this code.
And how did you come to realize
that it was being abused?
I take pride in my work.
I would dip into the system
and monitor it from time to time
just to make sure
that there wasn't anything going wrong.
Just to get ahead
of any potential problems.
And that's how you became aware
of what the bank
was really doing with the code.
Yeah. And I reported it immediately.
Who did you report it to?
Hey, Mr. Shaw, it's okay.
To him. To John Honaker.
Things are getting
really green with our mirror jury.
The real one's buying it, too.
You realize that you're breaking your NDA
- by testifying with us today?
- Of course.
But I'm dying.
What are they gonna do to me?
- Nice work, Counselor.
- Thank you.
By any chance would
you gentlemen be free right now?
For you? Never free. Always available.
My offices.
It's a shame we didn't have a towel.
We could have handed it
to her here and now
so she could throw it in.
Have Marissa call Cable's mother.
Put her on high alert
to come to court tomorrow.
Will do.
You understand this is a nuisance case
for my bank. Period.
It's bad PR, but PR is highly perishable.
All it takes is a couple
of news cycles and...
What's it doing for your stock price?
How many shares
does he personally control?
- 15 million.
- Ooh.
And every dollar it goes down...
If you're suggesting that I put
my personal net worth over
the safety of others...
That's not for us to decide.
We're comfortable leaving it to the jury.
We'll pay your client
$25 million to settle.
Obviously, I'm obliged to share
your offer with my client,
but I will strongly advise her
to reject it.
If you'll excuse me, have a
moment with my partner here.
And she does tend to take my advice.
I'm trying to be reasonable here.
I'm trying to put this all behind us.
Oh, well...
what do you know, it's not there.
What do you want?
I want him to hurt.
The way my client is gonna hurt
every time she walks
by her daughter's bedroom.
The way those families are hurting.
Mr. Colón, any idea why your witness
has chosen not to grace us
with his presence?
Uh, Your Honor, I know
that Mr. Shaw was most anxious
to be cross-examined,
and I know that with his illness,
mobility can sometimes be an issue.
We expect him any minute now.
I will give him another three minutes.
Yes, Your Honor.
Talk to me.
He's dead.
- What?
- I went to his apartment to pick him up,
and the ambulance
was already there. EMTs.
The cleaning lady found him.
Mr. Colón? Dr. Bull?
So, the judge gave us
a continuance until tomorrow.
He's also giving the
jury a stern instruction
to disregard all of Shaw's testimony.
Well, there you have it.
Can I ask a really horrible question?
Does anyone think it's just a coincidence
that that poor man
was found dead this morning?
For what it's worth,
everyone at the scene
believed they were looking
at natural causes.
There wasn't even a hint
of anything criminal.
From your lips.
Knock, knock.
What you thinking, Lincoln?
Someone looks unhappy.
I thought we were finished with you.
How'd you get in here?
I was over at Homeland,
and I stumbled across something
I thought you might find interesting.
Told Marissa all about it and...
And she gave you her credentials.
Doesn't she know that goes
on your permanent record?
Doesn't she know she's not gonna
get into a good college now?
Why do you look so sad?
Our key witness,
a whistleblower Danny found,
suddenly died before he could
complete his testimony.
I'm sorry.
Pulmonary embolism.
I had one of those a few months ago.
I heard.
Fun fact: if you want to poison somebody,
always choose potassium chloride.
Leaves no trace and presents
as pulmonary embolism.
Oh, my God.
This guy Honaker helped kill Cable.
I'm pretty sure he killed my witness.
And it looks like...
he's gonna go scot-free.
But that's not why you came here
in the middle of the night.
Is that for me?
Yeah, but...
now I'm not sure
if it's gonna help or hurt.
Try me.
Remember I told you
I had soft intel that suggested
Honaker and Gronsky
were together in Panama?
This is two days
after the bridge collapse
in Panama City.
Oh, my God.
This is great.
This changes everything.
It does, and it doesn't.
I cheated again.
I got that by hacking into an NSA server.
You can't use it.
If you introduce that photo,
I'll be behind bars in a matter of days.
Well, why'd you bring it to me?
I just...
sensed how badly you needed to know.
You were right all along.
I thought it was important.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Bull...
you can't use it.
I understand.
Can I have it, please?
No.
I think you should probably go now.
There's not a day gone by
since the tragedy
when I haven't wondered what
we could have done differently.
And what have you determined? I believe,
we honestly did the best we could.
You know, we handle over a
thousand transactions a second.
The possibility that we might miss
one errant financial anomaly,
one exchange,
though infinitesimally small,
obviously still exists.
And that's no excuse.
We have to do better.
We will do better.
To begin with, we've taken down
Mr. Shaw's code,
and we are in the process
of setting up
far more rigorous protocols.
Thank you, Mr. Honaker.
Nothing further.
Cross-examination?
Yes, Your Honor.
Just to clarify.
It sounds like you're suggesting
that the fault lies not with the bank,
and by extension, not with you,
but with the coding created
for you by the late Adam Shaw.
I take no pleasure
in speaking ill of the dead,
but clearly, his work was flawed.
Aah.
I don't know if I follow that.
I mean, he didn't make the software
that was supposed
to spot the transactions.
The government did that.
He made the software that allowed you
to circumvent the government safeguards.
Objection. Is counsel going
to ask a question,
or simply pontificate for the jury?
I apologize, Your Honor.
And yes, I-I do have a question.
Are you certain
you don't know an Ivan Gronsky,
the terrorist leader
who took down the bridge?
No. I do not.
As I've stated numerous times.
So, if you don't know Ivan Gronsky,
then how do you explain this photo...
Oh, my gosh.
Bull, you can't do that.
...which was
taken in Panama two days
after the I-99 collapsed?
That's you, isn't it,
with Mr. Gronsky,
together,
a week before the CIA and Interpol took
him and the rest of his team out?
Objection! We've never seen this photo.
We have complied with the court order
to turn over our documents.
For the plaintiff to sandbag us like this
is beyond the pale. Counsel, my chambers,
now.
Dr. Bull,
you, too.
There's no foundation
for this photo whatsoever.
It could have been photoshopped.
Okay, then. Mr. Colón,
Dr. Bull,
one of you had better tell me
where this photograph came from now.
It just surfaced this
morning on a small website.
Probably being picked up by all the
major media outlets as we speak.
For all we know, members
of the jury are looking at it
on their phones
while we're back here fighting.
Can't control the media.
As for the veracity of the photograph,
may I suggest, Your Honor,
that since her client is
already on the stand,
why don't we ask him to authenticate it?
He knows whether it's him or not,
and he certainly knows
whether he was there.
You're right. Of course he does.
Let's get back in there.
It's a simple question, sir.
Is that you in the photo or not?
I'd... have to study it to say for sure.
Really? That's what you're going with?
You know what you look like, don't you?
Objection.
Withdrawn.
I'll concede, it looks like me.
Looks like you?
Okay.
All right. All right, we'll go with that.
Uh... let me ask you another question.
Uh, this guy who looks like you?
He looks pretty angry in this picture.
Is it because his terrorist buddy
who'd been limiting his activities
to Eastern Europe
suddenly killed 37 Americans?
I mean, that must have
really turned up the heat
on you and the bank.
I'm sorry.
I mean... the heat
on the guy in this photo
who looks exactly like you.
No answer?
I understand.
It's a lot to digest.
But while you're thinking about it...
let me ask you.
How much did you and the bank
make with Gronsky?
I don't know off-hand.
Well, according to our analysis,
he moved hundreds of millions of
dollars a year through Thoreau.
Funding from foreign
governments, ransoms.
Over the last decade,
over a billion dollars.
Again,
I can't verify those numbers.
What about your year-end bonus
this past year?
Can you verify that?
$80 million.
$80 million. Wow.
Whew!
37 dead Americans
driving over that bridge,
trying to get home to their loved ones.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
In the above entitled action,
we find for the plaintiff
in the amount of $100 million.
- Thank you.
- Thank you... for letting us do this.
Oh, my God.
We did it.
And you.
You were amazing.
Oh, Cable was.
This was for her.
Yeah.
Hmm. I wish this felt better.
He doesn't look too unhappy.
Pocket change for him.
Just... wait a second.
John Honaker.
You're under arrest
for providing material aid
to terrorists, resulting
in multiple deaths.
You feel better now?
Yeah. I guess I do.
You know, everyone at
TAC still thinks it was me
that slipped that photo to
that anti-banking website.
Girl has to protect herself.
Soon as I realized you weren't
gonna give me the picture back,
I had to come up with a plausible reason
why it was out there.
Classic Homeland move, by the way.
Using a news outlet
to launder a photograph?
Oh.
- I may steal that from you.
- Hmm.
Unless, of course,
you've changed your mind
and want to come work for me,
in which case there'd be no point.
Well... that depends.
If I hadn't done what I did,
would you have sold me out?
Would you have used that photo?
I think you would have.
I think nothing matters more to
you than getting the bad guys.
I'm sorry.
Of course...
this bad guy had done something...
awful to a member of your team.
You were seeking justice for her.
Nothing for yourself.
I'd love to work for someone
who sticks up for me like that.
Excuse me?
I've already discussed money and
benefits and hours with Marissa.
Hours? We don't do hours.
I do.
But I promise you
you and your company will be
the second most important thing
in my life.
Second.
That's all I have to offer,
and I'm offering it to you.
Sold.
Mommy?
I believe you're being
summoned by Number One.
I believe he might have
just done a number two.
See you Monday.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com